ehhhhh...
Thank you very much.
I'll ask my senpai for some corn soup.
Corn pottage? Pomptage.
Line 4?
That way or the back?
We're halfway through.
It's like a block container.
Nice.
Lego.
This place is so small.
Kanchal is so expensive.
I wonder what it's like to have some kind of in
It's a system.
I wonder what it's like to be in an interview with someone who has historical ties to the city.
The naming is all assigned.
Please take the seat with the number on your express ticket.
Mr. Fuji.
There's also this factory feeling.
I like how it's like a sudden boom in the city
Turn it around.
Class is almost here
Too bad it's closed.
You can't see the scenery.
Everyone got off at Ise.
I'm a little worried. Thank you.
What's with all the luggage? Sister. I turned the movie on just before we got off. We only had a moment to get off.
Oh, no!
Can I put my coat on here?
Let's put it on. I want to wear it too!
Watch out! Watch out!
You're doing something I'm not used to!
I'm not used to this!
I've got it all.
I've got it all in my arms.
I'm getting ready on the platform at the station.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
This is how we arrived.
Sorry about the angle.
We're here.
What's going on?
I went through, but it rang.
I went through, and it rang.
Oh, that's it, isn't it?
Oh, shit!
What happened?
My parking ticket got jammed.
I got out, and then it just came back.
I called the clerk.
Excuse me, sir.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so where am I?
Suzukawa.
It's blurry.
I'm blurry!
Here we are!
We are going to Ise Jingu Shrine
to Ise Jingu Shrine
We're here to pray
We're going to take a bus now.
It's pretty far.
It was far.
About an hour and a half from Tokyo by bullet train?
Yes, about an hour and a half.
It took about an hour and a half on the limited express train.
That's pretty impressive.
It's a nice feeling.
It was my first time to take Kintetsu.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It's fun to play ping-pong.
I'm just vlogging like this because it's really just the two of us today.
I really came to hang out. You really came to hang out?
Just in case.
Thank you. That's nice.
I'm nervous about taking a bus in a city I don't know, but it sounds fun.
I'm so excited to play ping-pong with you... but it's fun...
The guy I was riding the express with...
I looked this way...
By the way, it's a 35 minute walk from Izutsugawa.
By the way, it's a 35 minute walk from Izutsugawa, and about 20 minutes by bus.
That's right.
That's because I was looking up "Inner Shrine.
It depends on where you get there.
If you take the bus, it's about 10 minutes.
So we're going to line up at the bus stop
We've arrived at Uchikyu-mae.
The air is so nice!
It feels like living here, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
It feels so nice, it feels so nice, it feels so nice, it feels so nice, it feels so nice, it feels so nice, it feels so nice, it feels so nice, it feels so nice
It feels good.
It's cold, but not that cold.
It's nice.
And you know what, I'm sure I'm doing this wrong, but...
Like this.
Right here, right here.
It's really nice.
It's nice.
I want some Ise udon.
I want some.
I want some... at Ise.
I heard there are some places in Ise where taking pictures is prohibited.
I'd like to take pictures
I'd like to take pictures.
Let's go.
It's the first time we're turning it in by ourselves.
Around Naik-san...
We haven't even looked up a map.
This is a little bit...
It's still on the camera. I wonder if I can see it like this.
Like this, like this, like this, like this.
Like this.
Oh, but it's already the torii gate!
Maybe I'm not allowed to take pictures after this torii.
That's fun.
Let's look at this torii then.
Right.
After this torii, it's not allowed to take pictures.
So I'll ask everyone to wait until we get to this point.
Let's pray!
It's too bright.
It's dazzling.
It's so bright.
It's shining brightly.
We were glowing.
I'm gonna go now.
We're shining so bright, we're shining so bright.
Thanks to you.
I'm here.
He's here.
Who's here?
Looks delicious.
All this time...
He says everything looks delicious. It's just before lunch.
I'm just starting to get hungry.
You went to the restaurant just inside and tried to stop by after you ate. I thought it was dangerous.
That's right.
It's the first restaurant you've been to.
First restaurant.
It's too early.
Too soon.
Too early
Hakkochin
I don't know if you guys are going for it or not!
Wow, metal stangos!
Oh my God!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, the meat sushi!
Oh, Matsusaka beef!
That was a little tempting, wasn't it?
You had it at many restaurants.
Yes, there were.
It's famous, isn't it?
It's very popular this time of year.
That's right.
There's the main store in Akafuku.
The main store is nice.
We should definitely go here.
Let's go.
So now I'm looking at various things.
We are looking.
Now, where will we go?
Think about it.
Okage Yokocho
Yes, that's right,
Leave Okage Yokocho for now,
Let's see, we are, you know, in the entertainment business, so we would like to go to Hiko-jinja Shrine where the god of entertainment is said to be.
I'd like to go to the Hiko-jinja Shrine, which is said to have a god of performing arts.
It was pretty impressive, wasn't it? It was just before noon.
Yes, it was.
Well, no thanks... my stomach was always in the center.
As soon as the stores open.
We both had an idea of where we wanted to go.
So we're going to go there.
So that's where we'd like to go. Before we go there?
Yes.
I want to go to the Sarutahiko Shrine.
I would like to enter.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to pay my respects.
But you know what? We came here without doing any research at all.
I didn't think the inner and outer sky were that far apart.
It's a little bit too far to walk.
That was a little too bulletproof.
Let's check it out next time.
It's a little shaky.
Sorry.
So, here we are at the Saltahiko Shrine.
Yay!
I'm going to pay my respects!
It's just a figure...
I drew this on the horse.
Here we go, here we go, here we go
Nineteen.
You remember?
Remember?
Don't you want to go in with Kaho?
Sure, sure.
I'll put it in then.
This way, this way.
They look so much alike.
Here.
Number 3838-38.
Oh!
Number 38.
Oh, uh, so how was your fortune?
Omikuji. Oh, yes, Omikuji.
Close to my face.
Slippery.
You're taller than me.
You're backlit. You can't see anything.
You can't see us.
I was the last lucky one.
I was lucky.
What about the small stuff?
There wasn't much praise.
They were pretty strict.
When I drew my New Year's omen...
But it was today.
Then you're doing much better.
Just a little better.
That's good.
Really.
Do you ever get a hot towel like this?
I don't.
I'm back after a long day like this.
Thanks to you, I'm here.
I'll bring it back and we'll have lunch.
Bye bye!
Before lunch
It's shaking.
Looks good.
Let's take some pictures.
Cheese, cheese, cheese.
That way!
That way! That's the color!
Wow, but it's so tingly.
How does it work?
It does.
Well, it's a chilli. How do you get it?
It's a chilli.
Bon appétit.
Then, please. I'll take it.
Then, I will have it. I will eat this.
Thank you for your hard work. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.
I came to see it right in front of me.
They're looking at me so much.
They're looking at me like that.
Right in front of you.
Look at it like that.
Look at me like that. Right in front of you right now.
See it like that?
See it a little bit like that?
A little bit of this.
And this.
Zenzai.
Oh, zenzai.
Can you take it over there? Over there.
I don't mind if we take it over there.
I'll go on.
The funny old geezers... ha-ha-ha...
It's delicious.
They're eating.
Delicious. Delicious.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Suddenly it feels like New Year's
It's a little late for that
Delicious!
Box
Just put the veggies in it.
Seriously, I've had three
I can't believe it's cancer.
Yay!
me
I'm glad you like it.
I'm glad you're here, thank you very much.
Oh, no!
Oh, it's growing!
Oh, it grows and grows and grows!
It stretches, it stretches, it stretches, it stretches, it stretches, it stretches, it stretches, it stretches...
Bon appétit!
Hot?
Okay, here we go.
Stretch.
Mmm.
Mm-hmm.
Nm
mmm
Hmmm... I'd like to head down to the lower sky now.
I think he might have said outer sky.
It's going to be below us.
There's a huge headwind headed our way.
We're headed down.
So we're heading down, too.
Have a good time.
The wind is coming down.
It's so bad!
Yes, it is.
It's a little bit in the shade.
It's getting chilly.
Amazing!
It's so shiny.
Amazing.
Amazing!
I forgot how hungry I am. I went around empty stomach because my mother's head is crumbling. That was fun.
You know, this is the first time you two have been here... on a bullet train, in private.
I feel like I got some nice vibes from you, but more than that, it was fun to spend time together.
It was fun. Yay!
That's great!
I want to come back again.
Yeah, let's go again. Let's go somewhere else.
We're not a good team.
It was fun, meme
Me.
me
me, me, me... The tracks are nice.
I love the train tracks.
There it is! There it is! There it is!
You went to that famous park, right?
Yes!
The tracks are nice.
The weather's nice.
The tracks are good
The tracks are good The tracks are good The tracks are good The tracks are good The tracks are good The tracks are good
The tracks are nice
The tracks are good
That's why
I went to a pancake shop earlier
Just because I went to a cafe earlier
Just because we went to a cafe...
From Mie Station
I'm going home.
We filmed the ending.
We did, but...
Afterwards...
I went to a cafe.
Tsukuyomi
Tsukuyomi no Mikoto
Tsukuyomi no Miyaka
That guy...
Say hello.
He's on his way back.
He said hello and left... and he's on his way back.
I saw him.
In my imagination, I found another coffee shop.
Pancakes.
Delicious!
Paris to Nagoya Station!
Pancakes!